// This JSON file contains the flashcard key:value array

$flashcards = [
  { 
    "front" : "ribera",
    "back" : "riverbank or shore"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "posada",
    "back" : "inn or lodging"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "señaladas",
    "back" : "appointed, posted or marked"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "ventura",
    "back" : "risky or dangerous undertaking"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "hallar",
    "back" : "find (something lost), discover, or come upon"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "ahondar",
    "back" : "deepend, delve into"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "deleite",
    "back" : "delight, pleasure"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "alabar",
    "back" : "to praise"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "provecho",
    "back" : "benefit, profit, advantage"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "animas",
    "back" : "soul (in purgatory), bore (as in cannon)"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "sayete",
    "back" : "war tunic"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "truhan",
    "back" : "shameless (adj), rascal (n)"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "loar",
    "back" : "to praise, to laud"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "holgar",
    "back" : "to be idle or unnecessary"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "maña",
    "back" : "knack/aptitude, swindle/hustle"
  },
  { 
    "front" : "aldea",
    "back" : "village or small town"
  },

  { 
    "front" : "molienda",
    "back" : "mill"
  },

  { 
    "front" : "caldero",
    "back" : "cauldron"
  },
  
  { 
    "front" : "mozuelo",
    "back" : "lad (f. gal)"
  },
  
  { 
    "front" : "agudeza",
    "back" : "sharp (both for blade or quick wit)"
  },

];